https://www.johnstonequipment.com/en/privacy-policy

CAREERS
FIND YOUR BRANCH:
Enter City or Postal Code:
Picking Automation
Automated Lift Guided Vehicles (AGV)
Picking Automation
Automated Lift Guided Vehicles (AGV)
Privacy Policy
Johnston Equipment is committed to protecting the privacy of each person who visits our web site.
Collection of personal information
At various locations throughout the site, you may elect to send us an e-mail or complete a response form. We only collect personal information from visitors if we need it in order to serve them properly.
We never collect any personal information (such as e-mail address, name or street address) unless a visitor has chosen to provide that information to us. We do not use techniques that collect personal information without your knowledge. We do not sell or provide any personal information submitted through our web site to third parties.
Access to personal information submitted through our web site is restricted to those employees who need to know about it in order to serve you properly. The personal information you submit through our web site is safeguarded using a secure password protection system. We will inform you of what personal information we have collected about you from our web site at your request. We will correct or update any personal information we have collected about you from our web site at your request.
Use of non-personal information
When you visit our site, we may automatically record certain non-personal information about your visit. We log a visitor's IP address, host name and time of visit. This limited non-personal information helps us to understand how traffic flows through our site. It also assists in our planning for new content and online services. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change this feature in your browser, so that you are notified each time a cookie is sent. You can also set most web browsers to block all cookies. Google Analytics is used to analyze traffic on this web site. Google analytics does not create individual profiles of visitors but only collects aggregate data.
E-mail for marketing purposes
From time to time, we will send e-mail messages to those who have opted-in to our electronic mail list. We use these messages to announce new product information, provide industry perspectives and to keep you informed of happenings at Johnston Equipment.
Every e-mail message includes the option to be removed from our mailing list. Our anti-spam commitment.
Policy updates
Johnston Equipment updates this privacy policy from time to time in order to comply with applicable legislation and privacy standards and to better serve our customers. Regardless of later updates, we will abide by the privacy practices described in this Policy at the time you provided us with your information.
Forklifts
Industrial Vehicles
Leasing & Financing
Services
Training
Warehouse Automation
Storage Solutions
About Us
